incredigames.com 2013-12-26

# Privacy Policy - IncrediGames Games

**NOTICE TO UNITED STATES AND OTHER NON-EUROPEAN UNION RESIDENTS:** This Privacy Policy is provided by Iplay. IPLAY IS A UNITED STATES COMPANY, and is the party responsible for the collection and maintenance of your information. 

**NOTICE TO EUROPEAN UNION RESIDENTS:** This Privacy Policy is provided by Iplay Enterprises. Iplay Enterprises is a Cyprus entity and is the party responsible for the collection and maintenance of your information. 

Your privacy is important to Iplay and Iplay Enterprises (together with their subsidiaries and affiliates, "Iplay") and our partners. We respect your privacy rights and recognize the importance of protecting the information we collect about you.

Iplay operates various web sites with game-related products and services (our "Sites") and provides applications for the provision of various online and mobile services, such as search and gaming (collectively, "Applications") through which personal information may be collected. This privacy policy (the "Privacy Policy") applies to all personal information collected by Iplay through our Sites and Applications. 

If Iplay is operating the Sites or Applications under an agreement with a specific partner, the branding of the Site or the Application will indicate the specific partner with which Iplay operates the Site or Application ("Identified Partners"). In such event, Iplay may share the data collected with that particular Identified Partner. Accordingly, Iplay´s use of your data is subject to our Privacy Policy - and our Identified Partner´s use of your data is subject to its privacy policy. You should familiarize yourself with such Identified Partner´s privacy policy. Some of Iplay´s Identified Partners serve their own ads or use other ad-serving networks. To opt out of data collection by an Identified Partner´s ad-serving network, please see that Identified Partner´s privacy policy. 

This Privacy Policy describes our practices regarding the information collected online through Sites and Applications maintained by Iplay, and not to web sites or services offered and operated by other companies or organizations to which we link. Additionally, this Privacy Policy does not cover information that we collect through other methods, such as mail-in sweepstakes.

Iplay is headquartered in the United States and the collected data is stored in the United States. Although we operate Sites and maintain some operations outside the United States, when you become a member of one of our online communities or programs, make a purchase from Iplay or register for one of the Applications, your account is with a United States company or European company, as applicable, and your data will be stored in the United States. 

BY USING THIS SITE, APPLICATION, OR USING ANY OF THE RELATED SERVICES, YOU SIGNIFY YOUR ASSENT TO IPLAY´S PRIVACY POLICY AND YOUR UNDERSTANDING THAT IPLAY MAY PROCESS YOUR DATA IN ACCORDANCE WITH THIS PRIVACY POLICY. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THE FOREGOING, PLEASE DO NOT USE THE SITE OR APPLICATION. 

## THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT

If you are a visitor to a Site or a user of an Application, you may provide us with two types of information: personal information you knowingly provide us on an individual basis ("Personal Information") and statistical and usage information collected using cookies and other technologies as you browse the Site or use an Application ("Usage Information").

## 1\. Personal Information

**Registration Information**  
You will need to provide us information about yourself, your firm or company, and your preferences when you register on one of the Sites or for one of the Applications. The specific information collected will vary depending on the Site or Application, and may include your name, email address, mailing address, birth date and gender. Registration is not required to browse any of our Sites, but you will not be able to view certain content or use aspects of certain Sites or Applications that require registration if you do not provide the requested information.

**Credit Card Information**  
If you choose to purchase products or services from us or our partners, you may need to provide a valid credit card number and expiration date, in addition to your name, mailing address, email address and phone number. Iplay does not store credit card information, but securely transmits it to our payment processors for verification and processing. 

**Email Information**  
In addition to providing us with your email address as part of registration, if you choose to correspond with us through email or by using a web interface to reach customer support, we may retain the content of your messages together with your email address and our responses.

## 2\. Usage Information

Similar to other commercial web sites, we utilize standard technologies such as "cookies," clear GIFs (also known as "web beacons" or "action tags") and web server logs to collect information about how the Sites and Applications are used. Additionally, when you connect to or download an Application, we may retrieve information from the computer used to log onto the Application. The information we collect may include technical information about your computer, system and application software, and peripherals, and any data related to the use and operation of the software applications used in connection with the Application. 

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a very small text document, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier. When you visit a web site, that site´s computer asks your computer for permission to store this file in a part of your hard drive specifically designated for cookies. We use the cookie to recognize your computer when you visit our Sites or use our Applications. Cookies can link to information regarding your account with us, pages you have viewed, or games you have played. This information is used to deliver content specific to your interests and to monitor web site or game usage. 

Information gathered through cookies and web server logs may include the date and time of visits, the pages viewed, time spent at the Site, and the web sites visited just before and just after the Site.

You can control your browser´s settings regarding cookies by selecting "Internet Options" (IE), "Options" (Firefox and Chrome) or "Preferences" (Safari) or in the "Tools" menu of your browser. This will allow you to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, have your browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or disable cookies altogether. However, some Applications and aspects of our Sites will not function properly if you do not accept cookies. 

**Clear GIFs**  
Clear GIFs are small, invisible graphic images (usually only one pixel) placed on a web page or email message to capture statistical usage information. They are not used to collect personal information about you.

**IP Addresses**  
An IP addresses is a number assigned to your computer every time you are connected to the Internet. IP addresses are automatically collected by our web server as part of demographic and profile data known as "traffic data" so that appropriate data (such as the web pages you request) and geographically relevant content can be sent to you.

**Referrers**  
A Referrer is the information passed along by a web browser that references the web URL you linked from, and is automatically collected by our web server as "traffic data." We use traffic data to credit your referral to a partner or affiliate who referred you to our Site or Application. This information may also be used by Iplay to identify broad demographic trends that may be used to provide information tailored to your interests. You are not personally identified from such use of this information.

**Omniture**  
In addition to our own internal tracking, we utilize the services of Omniture, Inc., a provider of online business optimization software, to assist us in the capture and analysis of customer usage and tracking information. Omniture acts as a limited agent of Iplay only for the purpose of providing such services. Any information obtained by Omniture from Iplay will be treated by Omniture as proprietary and confidential information. To view Omniture´s privacy policy, click here. If you do not wish to allow your session visitation information to be aggregated and analyzed by Omniture, you may utilize the opt-out mechanism found under the heading "Opt-out and update policies" here.

## ADVERTISING

**Our Advertisers**  
Iplay´s advertisers and advertising vendors display targeted advertisements. Although we do not provide any personal information to the advertiser or advertising vendor, by interacting with or clicking on an ad you acknowledge the possibility that the advertiser may assume you meet the targeting criteria used.

In addition to cookies placed by Iplay or its agents, as described above, advertisers and advertising vendors that serve ads onto our Sites may use their own cookies or other tracking technologies. We cannot be responsible for the privacy policies or practices of any such advertisers and vendors.

**AdTech**  
Iplay works with Adtech US, Inc. for the delivery of advertisements to certain Sites and Applications. The non-personally-identifiable information collected about your visits to the Sites may be used in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. You have the option to opt out of the collection of such information by clicking here and following the ad cookie opt-out instructions.

## HOW WE USE THE INFORMATION

**Uses of your Personal Information**  
Iplay will use your information primarily to provide you with our products and services and to receive payment from you. In order to do this, we may determine whether you meet the minimum system requirements to use our products. We may also ask you to participate in surveys about products, services, news and events; we may offer you product upgrades and games for you to purchase. You may opt out of some of these uses.

Iplay may also provide Personal Information to companies we engage as contractors or agents to perform services for us, such as maintaining software, providing email marketing or administering a sweepstakes or contest. Information will be shared with such contractors only to the extent reasonably necessary for them to perform these services on our behalf, and pursuant to confidentiality obligations.

**Uses of Usage Information**  
Usage Information may be used by Iplay to analyze Site and Application use in order to optimize the Site and the Applications and improve the user experience.

Iplay may use the information collected from your computer related to technical aspects of your connecting to a Site or Application in order to facilitate the provision of software updates, product support and other services to you (if any) related to the Sites and Applications, to verify compliance with the terms of the applicable Site or Application, to improve our products or services or to provide services or technologies to you.

## GENERALLY

**Where is the information held?**  
We are a global organization and the computer systems on which we collect, store, and use the information collected or received are based in the United States and elsewhere. Your personal information may be transferred to, used, processed or held by Iplay in the United States and in other countries, including both member and non-member countries of the European Union, and used for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy.

**Third-Party Disclosure of Personal Information**  
Iplay does not use your Personal Information for purposes incompatible with those listed above. Other than as provided in this Privacy Policy, Iplay does not provide your Personal Information to third parties unless you specifically consent to provide such information to a third party. Sometimes, certain indirectly identifiable information needs to be communicated with third-party vendors, for example, to process an order that you have made. We may also disclose Personal Information when legally compelled to do so. In other words, when the law requires it or when we have reason to believe that a disclosure is necessary or appropriate to address potential or actual injury or interference with the rights, property or operations of Iplay, our users or others. Finally, if we undergo a merger or acquisition, or sell or otherwise transfer substantially all the assets of Iplay, or relating to any web site that we own or operate or any product or service that we offer, Personal Information may be transferred to our successor or assign.

**Selected Notifications**  
Occasionally, we may also use the information we collect to notify you about new services and special offers we think you will find valuable. We will send you this type of communication only if we have received your permission to do so.

**How Does Iplay Protect Your Information and Secure Information Transmissions?**  
We use industry standard technology and services to protect and secure your information. We will never initiate any email communication with you that requests your private information. In general, we request that you do not send private information to us by email. Please contact Iplay support if you have any questions or concerns.

**Employee Access, Training and Expectations**  
Our corporate values, ethical standards, and practices are committed to the appropriate protection of customer and visitor information. In general, our business practices limit employee access to confidential information, and limit the use and disclosure of such information to authorized persons, processes and transactions.

**What About Other Web Sites Linked to Our Web Site?**  
We are not responsible for the practices employed by web sites linked to or from our Sites or accessed through our Applications, nor the information or content contained in any search results or third-party web sites. Often links to other web sites are provided solely as pointers to information on topics that may be of interest to the users of our Sites or Applications. Please remember that when you use a link to go from a Site to another web site, our Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. Your browsing and interaction on any other web site, including web sites which have a link on one of our Sites, is subject to that web site´s own rules and policies. Please read over those rules and policies before proceeding.

**Your Consent**  
By using any of our Sites or Applications, you consent to our collection and use of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy.

**Modification of Privacy Policy by Iplay**  
Iplay reserves the right to change or update this Privacy Policy at any time by posting a notice that we are changing this Privacy Policy. If there is a change to this Privacy Policy, we will post the change on the Site or with the Application to keep you aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we may disclose it. You will be deemed to have accepted such change if you continue to use the Site or Application after the new policy has been posted.

Effective: April 25, 2012
